thecgisite.com 2001-11-01

# TheCgiSite.com: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices of [http://www.thecgisite.com](http://www.thecgisite.com/). To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have disclosed our information practices and will notify you of: What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site. The organization collecting the information. How the information is used. With whom the information may be shared. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under TheCgiSite.com's control and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

**Information Collection and Use**

TheCgiSite.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. TheCgiSite.com collects information from our users at several different points and uses this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but does not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. 

**What are cookies?**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, some features on our site may not work as intended. 

**What other information do you request?**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name, e-mail address and mailing address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. We maintain a "No-Spam" policy, that means that we will not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail or mailing address to third-parties, without your consent. 

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. TheCgiSite.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. TheCgiSite.com does not store this information in its database after the user sends a one-time email. In addition, if a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. However, subscribers may contact TheCgiSite.com at [newsletter@thecgisite.com?body=REMOVE](mailto:newsletter@thecgisite.com?body=REMOVE) to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**

TheCgiSite.com will only share aggregated demographic information with partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties which receive the information. 

**What else should I know about my privacy when online?**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that TheCgiSite.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to this website. 

TheCgiSite.com uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Consent To This Agreement**

TheCgiSite.com is provided on an "as is" basis and makes no representations or warranties of any kind with respect to this website or its contents. By downloading, modifying, copying, viewing, or using this website, you agree that neither the author of this site nor the owners or administrators are liable for any breach of security, damages of any kind, including compensatory, direct, indirect or consequential damages, loss of data, income or profit, loss of or damage to property and claims of third parties. You also consent to the collection and use of information as specified above.
